Overview

Self-motivated and enthusiastic worker with vast experience in many different fields, having excellent collaboration, prioritization, and problem-solving skills. As a curious and fast learner, I'm excited about progressing in my career trajectory shift from the financial field to the world of tech, with a major focus on front-end development.

Key Skills and Attributes

- Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, TypeScript, NodeJS, Git.
- Creative and Innovative thinker
- Great self-learning and problem-solving skills
- Excellent team player and effective communicator
- Patience and attention to detail
- Fluent in Mandarin and English

Qualifications, Traning and Affiliations

React - The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux)
Intro Git & GitHub

Udemy

Learning Paths – Professional

Complete Intro React & Intermediate React

TypeScript Fundamentals

Deep JavaScript Foundations

CSS Grid & Flexbox for Responsive Layouts

Web Performance Fundamentals

Learning Paths – Beginner

Complete Intro to Web Development (HTML &CSS)

Getting Started with CSS

Getting Started with JavaScript

JavaScript: From fundamentals to functional JS

Website Accessibility

Bachelor of Commerce (Finance and International Business)

Monash University

Projects

Personal Portfolio

- Project description: A clean and simple personal portfolio website
- Technology involved: React, HTML, CSS
- Live Demo: https://blingblingda.github.io/react-resume-belinda
- Key contents:

Frontend Masters

- ✓ A React website with responsive design.
- ✓ Data-driven UI
- ✓ HTML5 + CSS3

Adopt Me

- Project description: A single-page web app for helping people adopt animals.
- Technology involved: React, HTML, CSS, TypeScript, Jest, Node.js
- Live Demo: https://blingblingda.github.io/adopt-me
- Key contents:
 - ✓ Using React State Hook for state management.
 - ✓ Loading data via React Effect Hook and Fetch.
 - ✓ Handling state errors in react hook.
 - ✓ Using Jest for unit tests.

Food Ordering

- Project description: An online food ordering website demo.
- Technology involved: React, HTML, CSS, Node.js
- Live Demo: https://blingblingda.github.io/food-order
- Key contents:
 - ✓ A single-page application built by React
 - ✓ Using CSS Module
 - ✓ Using firebase as a backend

Work Experience

Cross-departmental collaboration experience

- Built model with marketing and delivery team to estimate marketing event cost and profit, facilitating sales staff to sign event agreements with restaurants.
- Worked as a consultant from the financial team to discuss new software features with the IT department and provided some recommendations for software upgrades.
- As a consultant from the education department, worked with visa and migration department
 consultants to help the marketing department organise and plan marketing events based on the latest
 policies of institutes and government, and provided clients with professional advice on studying and
 immigration at the event.

Team Work

• Participated in Australian team meetings, effectively cooperated with the team to complete preparation of various financial statements, diagnosis of financial health, production/analysis of financial reports, etc. Won Dream Team Award for 2021.

- Worked with teammates to create export documents, reviewed and managed export certificates, tracked the delivery of each batch of goods and checked the relevant data to ensure a smooth international export delivery.
- Worked as a consultant team member to assist students with choosing institutions and courses, completing application forms and related paperwork, and applying for a student visa.

Planning & Organizing skills

- Created a plan for a financial software change, ensuring all financial data had been organized and migrated smoothly and accurately on time.
- Prepared and analyzed financial reports, organized monthly financial review meetings, explained financial statements to the management team and helped them to draw attention to important aspects of the financial data.
- Communicated with clients effectively and designed an ideal service plan by considering different applicants' requirements and processing progress.

Training and presentation experience

- Prepared quarterly financial knowledge training for the sales department, mainly focusing on explaining the company's latest financial policies, marketing event financial models, and restaurant partners' frequently asked questions.
- Organized semi-annual personal tax information sessions for all employees of Australian branches, focusing on individual tax returns and the latest tax policies.
- Received regular training from universities and institutes about updated information, then gave a
 presentation to team members, and explained the latest news.

Work History

HungryPanda AU Pty Ltd	MAR 2020 – JUN 2022
Accountant	
Orient International Holding Shanghai Textiles IMP.& EXP.Co.Ltd	JAN 2018 – DEC 2019
Import&Export Documentation Specialist	
OzStudy Group Migration & Education Agent	SEP 2016 – AUG 2017
Education Consultant	
Provence Café	JAN 2015 – JUL 2016
Assistant Accountant	